Let's kick things off with a brief introduction
to the Intel distribution of OpenVINO toolkit.
The OpenVINO toolkit name comes from
open visual inferencing and neural network optimization, not wine.
As the name implies,
it is largely focused around optimizing neural network inference and it's open source.
It's developed by Intel and help support fast inference across Intel CPUs,
GPUs, FPGAs, and the Neural Compute Stick with a common API.
You can take models built with multiple different frameworks,
like TensorFlow or Caffe,
and use its model optimizer to optimize for inference.
Once a model is put through the model optimizer,
you can use it with the inference engine,
which helps speed inference on the related hardware.
There's also a wide variety of
pre-trained models already put through the model optimizer,
which we'll cover in this lesson as well as those later lessons for the other components.
So how does this relate to AI at the Edge?
By optimizing for model speed and size,
this software enables running at the Edge.
Note that this does not mean an increase in inference accuracy.
This needs to be done in training beforehand.
The smaller, quicker models the software generates,
along with the hardware optimizations it provides,
are great for lower resource applications.
An Internet of things device, for instance,
doesn't have the benefit of the Cloud where it might have
multiple GPUs and almost unlimited memory space to run its applications.