As mention before, there are
a lot of pre-trained models available directly in the software.
Let's take a quick look at what pre-trained models are and how they are used.
Pre-trained models referred to models where retraining has already occurred.
This can lead to high even cutting-edge accuracy and
avoids the need for large-scale data collection and long costly training.
Given knowledge of how to preprocess inputs and handle the outputs,
you can plug these directly into your own app.
In the toolkit, pre-trained models refers specifically to
the Model Zoo containing pre-trained models already converted using the model optimizer.
As such, you can use these models directly with the inference engine.
You seen this slide before,
but here's just a quick visual reminder on how you can feed
the pre-trained model directly into the inference engine.
Before we get into the full set of pre-trained models available in the OpenVINO toolkit,
let's cover some of the basics of computer vision models first.